[{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In the 1974 film Twisted Brain, the homicidal boy turned into a monster by drinking a chemical. He was was shot by a character portrayed by which NFL player?", "correct_answer": "Mean Joe Greene", "incorrect_answers": ["Roger Staubach", "Chuck Noll", "John Niland"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "This town, closely linked to the legend of the Loch Ness monster, lies at the mouth of the river Ness.", "correct_answer": "Inverness", "incorrect_answers": ["Glenny", "Urquhart", "Aberdeen"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What are common side effects of pregnancy?", "correct_answer": "All of the these", "incorrect_answers": ["Stretch marks", "Morning Sickness", "Weight gain"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What was the full name of the character played by Al Pacino in the movie Scarface?", "correct_answer": "Antoino Tony Montana", "incorrect_answers": ["Tony Montana", "Anthony Tony Montana", "Ant Tony Montana"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Vitamin B12, which is related to hair growth and strength, can be obtained from which food?", "correct_answer": "All of these", "incorrect_answers": ["Diary products and egg yolks", "Seafood", "Meat"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In medical jargon, what is a Well Woman Exam?", "correct_answer": "A routine gynaecologic exam", "incorrect_answers": ["A full physical examination on a female adult who has no medical problems", "An exam on the doctor by a female who is well", "An exam on a female which finds herself to be well"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Starfish are capable of both asexual and sexual reproduction.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What notable feature does the Fennec Fox possess, that makes it easily recognizable?", "correct_answer": "Very large ears", "incorrect_answers": ["It has no tail", "Bluish fur", "Red eyes"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What does the name Zachary mean?", "correct_answer": "God has remembered", "incorrect_answers": ["Gods servant", "Gift from God", "Warlike"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Name the lucky winner of the 1999 Golden Raspberry Award for Worst Picture.", "correct_answer": "Wild Wild West", "incorrect_answers": ["Star Wars Episode I: The Phantom Menace", "The Haunting", "The Blair Witch Project"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Alexander Graham Bell, known as the inventor of the telephone, is also credited with the invention of this device, which was first used after the assassination of President James Garfield.", "correct_answer": "metal detector", "incorrect_answers": ["phonograph", "audiometer", "air conditioning"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What alias did Benjamin use when checking into the Taft Hotel in the film The Graduate?", "correct_answer": "Mr. Gladstone", "incorrect_answers": ["Mr. Doe", "Mr. Smith", "Mr. Billings"]}]